Guide to the Veranus A. Moore Papers, 1836-1958
Moore, Veranus A. papers, 1836-1958
- Series IV. Writings
  - "Report of the Committee on Standard Methods for the Preparation of Tuberculin and Mallein, ca. 1904 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - "Report of the Committee on Tuberculosis", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - "The Responsibility of Producing Safe Milk", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - "The Role of the Veterinarian in the Prevention and Control of Infectious Diseases" (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - "The Safety of Market Milk", Dec. 18, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - "Septicemia Hemorrhagica", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Smallpox Vaccination, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - "Some Facts about New York City as a Center of Veterinary Medical Education", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - "Some Problems for the Veterinarian", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - "Some Uses of Arsenic and Its Effect on Plants and Animals" (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - "A Sound Herd as the Unit" (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - "Statement made a Hearing on the Wicks Bill for the Protection of Certain Domestic Animals and Encouraging the Sheep Industry" (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - "Studies on Hog Cholera" [fragment], n.d. (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - "Studies on Undulant Fever in Its Relation to Bang Abortion Disease" (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - "A Study of Tubercle Bacteria in Milk and Feces of Tuberculin Reacting Cows", 1909 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - "Swine Diseases", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Synopsis of Lectures in Bacteriology
    - Annotated Chapters [incomplete], n.d. (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Proofs, ca. 1905 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Ch. 1. General, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Ch. 2. Morphology and Classification (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Ch. 3. General Biology of Bacteria, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Ch. 4. Culture Media, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Ch. 5. Sterilization, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Ch. 6. Isolation, Cultivation and Identification of Bacteria (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Ch. 8. Pathogenic Bacteria, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Ch. 9. Pyogenic Bacteria, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Ch. 17. Diphtheria, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Ch. 18. Anaerobic Methods, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Ch. 19. Miscellaneous Pathogenic Bacteria, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Ch. 21. Bacteria in Water, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Typescript, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Proofs, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - "Synopsis of Talk on Bacteria", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - "Trichinosis in Children", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Tubercle Bacteria Cultivation, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - "The Tuberculin Test", 1897 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Tuberculosis, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - " Tuberculosis: A Summary", 1904 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - "Tularemia: A New Disease of Rabbits", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - "Undulant Fever", 1926 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Undulant Fever, Sep. 1929 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - "Undulant Fever", Jan. 15, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - "Undulant Fever", Feb. 1930 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - "Undulant Fever", 1930 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - "Undulant Fever in Man Associated with Bacteria Indistinguishable from Brucella Abortus" (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - "Vaccines, Bacterins, Phylacogens, Antitoxins and Serums" (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - "Value of Animal Experimentation", 1926 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - "The Value of Experimentation in the Control of Animal Diseases", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - "The Value of Tuberculin in the Control of Tuberculous Herds", Sep. 1908 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - "The Veterinarian of the Future", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - "The Veterinary Curriculum", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - "Veterinary Education", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - "Veterinary Education", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - "Veterinary Education" [fragment], ca. 1910 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - The Veterinary Profession, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - "The Veterinary Profession: It's Requirements and Opportunities", ca. 1914 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - "The Veterinary Situation", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - "The Veterinary Situation", Jan. 9, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - "The Veterinary Situation in New York State", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - "Veterinary Trend Now Countryward" (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Von Behring Tuberculosis Vaccine, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - "What Dairymen Should Know about Tuberculosis", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - "What is Meat Inspection", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - "What Science has done for Christianity", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - "Why We Must Have Veterinarians", 1926 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Women in Medicine, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Miscellaneous Articles and Essays, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Miscellaneous Speech Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Miscellaneous Proofs, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Fragments, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Series V. Subject Files
  - Agar Agar, ca. 1915 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Anaconda Copper Mining Company Case
    - Newspaper Articles, 1907-1910 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Court Opinions, 1909, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Synopsis of Testimony, ca. 1909 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Background and Support Material, ca. 1909 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Examination Reports, June-July 1906 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Examination Reports, 1905-1906 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Slide Reports, ca. 1906 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, ca. 1906 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Blueprints and Newsclippings, 1908-1909, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Anthrax, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Bacillus e. Spermophile, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Bacteria, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Bacteriology, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Bacteriology Lecture Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Biographies and Obituaries, 1891-1923 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Biographies of Emil Von Behring, Robert Koch and August Wasserman (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Blackleg, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Bovine Tuberculosis and Meat Inspection, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Bovine Tuberculosis and Meat Inspection, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Brucellosis and Undulant Fever, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Brusteuche, ca. 1913 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Cattaraugus County and Milbank Memorial Fund, 1923-1928 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Cattaraugus County and Milbank Memorial Fund, 1929-1930, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Cattaraugus County and Milbank Memorial Fund - Book of Test Results and Conclusions, ca. 1922-1923 (Box 34)
  - Child Health [ See also Series III. Correspondence-Government Agencies-US-White House Conference on Child Health and Protection.], ca. 1925-1930 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Civil Engineering, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Dairy Inspection and Milk Bourne Disease, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Diseased Animal Legislation, 1904-1929 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Foot (Hoof) and Mouth Disease, 1914-1925 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Fowl Plague, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Glanders, ca. 1908 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Glanders, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Herd Counts, ca. 1900-1930 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Hog Cholera, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Immunity, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Industrial Education and Reform, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Inoculation Records, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - International Commission on the Control of Bovine Tuberculosis [ See also Series III. Correspondence under same heading ]
    - Scrapbook, section 1, 1910-1911 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, section 2, 1910-1911 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, section 3, 1910-1911 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook, section 4, 1910-1911 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - International Veterinary and Medical Literature, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Ithaca and Tompkins County Public Health Publications, 1913-1929 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Jacob Dold Packing Co. Disease Chart, 1912 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - John's Disease, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Loomis Sanatorium Cow Temperature Charts, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Lymphangitis in Horses, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - McAnn, Alfred, 1913, 1915, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Meat Inspection, 1904, 1907, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Meat Packing Plant Inspection Reports, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Medical Education Literature, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Medical Education Literature, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Medical Education Literature, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Medical Education Literature, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Milk, 1904-1909 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Milk, 1910-1911 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Milk, 1912-1915 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Milk, 1916-1921 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Milk, 1923-1930, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Milk Correspondence, 1915-1916 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Milk Legislation, 1915-1918 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Milk Reading Notes, ca. 1915-1916 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Milk - Bacterial Count Chart for NY producers and dealers (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Nephrites, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - New York State Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Veterinary Service, Annual Report, 1912-1913 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - New York State Veterinarians, ca. 1890-1914 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - New York State Veterinary College Legislation, 1897-1923 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Pathology Lecture Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Physiology / Anatomy, 1899-1936 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Poultry, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Pseudotuberculosis, ca. 1888 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Public Health, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Public Health Regulations and Sanitary Codes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Public Health Regulations and Sanitary Codes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Public Health Regulations and Sanitary Codes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Public Health Regulations and Sanitary Codes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Rabies, ca. 1849-1930 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Rabies Quarantine Chart, ca. 1908 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Sanitation / Disinfection, 1883-1903 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Sanitation / Disinfection, 1904-1909 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Sanitation / Disinfection, 1910-1911 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Sanitation / Disinfection, 1912-1917, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Science Education, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Sex Education and Venereal Disease, ca. 1900-1920 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Sex Education and Venereal Disease, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Sex Education and Venereal Disease, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Sex Education and Venereal Disease, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Sex Education and Venereal Disease, ca. 1910-1930 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sex Education and Venereal Disease, ca. 1910-1930 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sex Education and Venereal Disease, ca. 1910-1930 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Sex Education and Venereal Disease, ca. 1910-1930 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Smallpox, 1899-1915, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Student Army Training Course on Hygiene and Sanitation (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Swine, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Tuberculin Observations, 1878 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Tuberculin and Mallein Record, 1905-1909 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Tuberculin and Mallein (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Tuberculosis, ca. 1899 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Tuberculosis, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Tuberculosis, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Tuberculosis, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Tuberculosis Advisory Board, 1908 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Tuberculosis Europe Trip, 1909 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Tuberculosis Legislation, 1908, 1920-1928 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Tuberculosis Research / Experiments, 1909-1910, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Tuberculosis Tests of New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Dairy Herd, 1909-1911 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tuberculosis - Miscellaneous, ca. 1900-1923 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - United States Army Veterinary Corps [ See also Series III. Correspondence-Government Agencies-U.S.- War Department/U.S. Army .], 1914-1916 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - United States Army Veterinary Corps, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - United States Army Veterinary Corps, 1918-1921 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - United States Army Veterinary Corps, 1922-1928 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - United States Army Veterinary Corps, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Veterinary Education Literature [ See also Series III. Correspondence-Government Agencies-NY-Department of Agriculture and Markets -and- Civil Service Commission .], ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Veterinary Education Literature, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Veterinary Education Literature, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Veterinary Qualifications Legislation, 1895-1927 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Vivisection
    - General, 1890-1899 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - General, 1900-1923 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - General, 1938-1958, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Newsclippings, 1896-1899 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Anti-Vivisection Organizations, ca. 1899-1910 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Medical Society of the State of New York, Committee on Experimental Medicine, 1908-1909 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Vivisection and Animal Cruelty Legislation, 1909-1920, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - World War I and the League of Nations [ See also Series III. Correspondence-Government Agencies-NY-Patriotic Agricultural Service Committee], ca. 1900-1925 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Reading Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Reading Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Reading Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Reading Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Reading Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Research Notes, ca. 1911-1913 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Research Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Research Notes, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Notes Found in Ziegler's Pathology (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Veterinary Publications, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Veterinary Publications, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Veterinary Publications, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Education Publications, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Medical Publications, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Index card files - article, book and serial citations, ca. 1885-1895 (Box 33)
- Series VI. Ephemera
  - Advertisements, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Advertisements, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Advertisements, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Advertisements, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Programs and Brochures
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1907-1929 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - American Association of Pathologists and Bacteriologists, 1901-1929, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - American Public Health Association, 1897-1919 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - American Public Health Association, 1920-1924, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1901-1912 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1913-1915 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1916-1929 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1899-1930 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1912-1930, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association - Welcome Ad: "Their Friends are in the City", 1925 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Colleges and Universities, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Congress of American Physicians and Surgeons, 1894-1925 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Cosmos Club, 1901-1929, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Freemasonry [ See also Freemasonry Handbooks and Series III. Correspondence-Freemasons.], ca. 1890-1930 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Freemasonry, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Freemasonry, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Freemasonry, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Freemasonry, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Freemasonry, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Freemasonry (includes poster advertising "Balbec Grotto's Smoker and Pot-LatchA program dealing exclusively with the Indians of our state and the northwestmusic by genuine redskins"), ca. 1890-1930 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Freemasonry (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - George Washington University, 1890-1895 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - George Washington University, 1898-1927, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Medical Society of the State of New York, 1901-1923, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - New York Farming Associations, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - New York State Veterinary Medical Association, 1895-1925 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - New York University, 1917-1921 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - New York University - "Are Two State Vet Colleges Needed" article by Pierre Fish, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Nu Sigma Nu, 1900-1915 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 1920-1927 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Phi Sigma Kappa, 1899-1927 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Rotary Club, 1918, 1927-1929 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Sigma Xi, 1895-1902 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Sigma Xi, 1903-1930, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1900-1917 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1919-1928, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Tompkins County Medical Society, 1903-1931 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - United States Livestock Sanitary Association, 1909-1925, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - World War I, ca.1917-1919 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, ca.1890-1930 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, ca.1890-1930 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, ca.1890-1930 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, ca.1890-1930 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Posters, Maps, etc.
    - American Veterinary Medical Association - Welcome Ad: "Their Friends are in the City", 1925 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association Conference Poster, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Cornell Exam Schedule, 1898-1899 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Cornell Communicable Disease Regulations, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Cornell Department of Agriculture Insecticide Spray Calendar, 1896 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Iowa State Veterinary School Ad., 1912 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Ithaca Mosquito Extermination Guide, 1905 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Mulford Laboratory Rabies Vaccination Ad, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - New York State Department of Agriculture Anthrax Notice, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - New York State Department of Agriculture Dairy Cow Law Announcement, 1914 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - New York State Department of Health Charts - Communicable Diseases Among Schoolchildren, ca.1916 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Dog/Rabies Quarantine Poster, 1903 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Russell Sage Foundation Chart - Spelling Ability Scale, ca. 1919 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture Fowl Pest Poster, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Bureau of Animal Industry Map of "Boundary Line of the District Infected with Splenetic or Southern Fever of Cattle", 1896 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Bureau of Animal Industry Hog Cholera Announcement, 1892 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - University of Nebraska Swine Disease Poster, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Walker-Gordon [Farms] News, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Pins
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1896, 1909, 1910 (Box 31)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1911, 1914, 1916 (Box 31)
    - American Lung Association, n.d. (Box 38)
    - American Public Health Association, 1901, 1902, 1924 (Box 38)
    - American Red Cross?, 1919 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1901 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1904 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1907-1910 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1912 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1917 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1918 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1920 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1922 (Box 38)
    - AVMA, 1923 (Box 38)
    - AVMA - Alexander Liautard Memorial, 1913 (Box 31)
    - "A Man May Be Down But He's Never Out", 1920 (Box 38)
    - British Medical Association, 1897 (Box 38)
    - Conference of Sanitary Officers of New York State, 1906, 1907, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Congo State, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Cornell University Class of 1887, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Genesse Valley Medical Association, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Grange Day at New York State Fair, 1920 (Box 38)
    - Holstein Friesian Association of America, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Liberty Loan and Liberty Bond, ca. 1917-1919 (Box 38)
    - National Grange Jubilee, 1916 (Box 38)
    - New York State Agricultural Society, 1916, 1922, 1926 (Box 38)
    - New York State Breeders Association, 1910, 1911, 1913 (Box 38)
    - New York State Breeders Association, 1917-1920 (Box 38)
    - New York State Dairymen's Association, 1908, 1909 (Box 38)
    - New York State Grange, 1918 (Box 38)
    - New York State Veterinary Medical Society, 1916, 1919, 1922 (Box 38)
    - Patrons of Husbandry, Tompkins, 1917 (Box 38)
    - Society for the Promotion of Agricultural Science, 1896 (Box 31)
    - Tompkins County War Chest, ca. 1917-1919 (Box 38)
    - Tuberculosis Conference, Hartford, CT, 1922 (Box 38)
    - United States Live Stock Sanitary Association, 1910, 1911 (Box 38)
    - Veranus Moore tie bar (Box 38)
    - War Savings Service, ca. 1917-1918 (Box 38)
    - Unidentified - "22nd Annual Meeting, Brooklyn", 1911 (Box 38)
    - Unidentified Medallion, possibly Masonic, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Buttons
    - 8th International Veterinary Congress?, 1905 (Box 38)
    - American Public Health Association, 1897, 1903, 1909 (Box 38)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1911, 1919, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Ithaca Masonic Temple, 1926 (Box 38)
    - New York State Veterinary Medical Association, 1912 (Box 38)
    - United States Live Stock Sanitary Association, 1913-1921 (Box 38)
  - Ribbons
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1891 (Box 38)
    - American Society of Microscopists, 1887 (Box 38)
    - A.A.A.C.E.S., Washington, D.C., 1908 (Box 38)
    - Columbian University, n.d. (Box 31)
    - Cornell Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 31)
    - Knights Templar, 1919 (Box 38)
    - "Local Committee", n.d. (Box 31)
    - Microscopical Society, n.d. (Box 31)
    - New York State Veterinary Medical Society and Eastern States Tuberculosis Eradication Conference, 1924 (Box 38)
    - Tompkins County Shrine Association, n.d. (Box 31)
    - Veterinary Medical Association of New Jersey, 1903 (Box 31)
  - Scrapbook
    - Items Removed from Scrapbook Pages, 1908-1919 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Items Loose in Scrapbook - Class Schedules, 1912-1917, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Items Loose in Scrapbook - Veterinary Remedies, ca. 1880-1920 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Items Loose in Scrapbook - Miscellaneous Programs, 1909-1920 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Items Loose in Scrapbook - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Calling Cards, ca. 1875-1930 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Club and Association Cards, ca. 1890-1930 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Travel Documents, ca. 1900-1910, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, ca.1890-1930 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Winnipeg Scrapbook, ca. 1910 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Cast Lists from Theatricals, ca. 1887-1896 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Bibles, 1848, 1876, 1892 (Box 31)
  - Fenelon's Pious Reflections for Every Day in the Month, ca. 1830s (Box 31)
  - Freemasonry Handbooks [ See also Pamphlets and Brochures-Freemasonry ], 1867-1925 (Box 31)
  - Wood block with Veranus Moore's image, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Stamp with Veranus Moore's signature, n.d. (Box 32)
- Series VII. Family Papers
  - Slawson and Moore Genealogy, ca.1890-1925 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Alva Moore
    - Bank Book, 1836 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Account Book, 1862 (Box 35)
    - Diary, 1861 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Diary, 1862 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Diary, 1866 (Box 25, Folder 10)